Cheney Brothers Silk Manufacturing Company Records 1984.0026
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series II: Personnel Records, 1860-1962
  - Subseries E: Employee Record Cards, 1860-1960
    - Male employee record cards, 1900-1940
      - Osb - Sa (Box 31)
      - Sch - U (Box 32)
      - V - Z (Box 33)
    - Female employee record cards, 1900-1940
      - A - B (Box 34)
      - C - Doy (Box 35)
      - Dra - Hal (Box 36)
      - Ham - K (Box 37)
      - L - Me (Box 38)
      - Mi - P (Box 39)
      - Q - Sto (Box 40)
      - Str - Z (Box 41)
    - Employee withholding cards, New York City and Manchester, CT offices, 1940-1956
      - New York, A - Z (Box 42)
      - Manchester, A - O
      - Manchester P - Z (Box 43)
    - Employee record cards, 1940-1956
      - A - M (Box 44)
      - N - Z, A - C (Box 45)
      - D - Mif (Box 46)
      - Mih - Z (Box 47)
- Series III: Labor Relations Records, 1930-1974
  - Subseries A: Arbitration, 1930-1974
    - Break even cost comparisons, 1952 (Box 48:, Folder 280)
    - Financial reports figures, 1952 (Box 48:, Folder 281)
    - Memo of decision (court case), 1952 (Box 48:, Folder 282)
    - Court case submissions, 1952 (Box 48:, Folder 283)
    - Mills having wage reductions, 1952 (Box 48:, Folder 284)
    - Pension cost, 1946-1952 (Box 48:, Folder 285)
    - Pioneer problems, 1952 (Box 48:, Folder 286)
    - Post hearing and reply brief, 1953 (Box 48:, Folder 287)
    - Publicity—proposed and actual, 1952-1953 (Box 48:, Folder 288)
    - Salaries, 1946-1951 (Box 48:, Folder 289)
    - Wage comparisons and union minutes, 1952 (Box 48:, Folder 290)
    - Brief, 1952 (Box 48:, Folder 291)
    - Pioneer Parachute Company, 1950-1953 (Box 48:, Folder 292)
    - Financial, 1938-1952 (Box 48:, Folder 293)
    - Labor relations, 1940-1952 (Box 48:, Folder 294)
    - Prices, 1950-1952 (Box 48:, Folder 295)
    - Sales competitors, 1952-1953 (Box 48:, Folder 296)
    - Scheibers award and opinion, 1953 (Box 48:, Folder 297)
    - Special reports for arbitration case, 1953 (Box 48:, Folder 298)
    - Straight time earnings vs. Expected earnings, 1953 (Box 48:, Folder 299)
    - Supreme Court of the United States, 1954 (Box 48:, Folder 300)
    - Textile Workers Union of America/C.I.O. brief, 1953 (Box 48:, Folder 301)
  - Subseries B: Agreements and Contracts, 1934-1956
    - Contract data, 1937-1941 (Box 48:, Folder 302-304)
    - Date—union contract, 1942 (Box 48:, Folder 305)
    - Vacation contract data, 1937-1945 (Box 48:, Folder 306)
    - Contracts, 1939-1941 (Box 48:, Folder 307-312)
    - Quotations from contracts, 1939 (Box 48:, Folder 313)
    - Exclusive collective bargaining agent, 1938-1940 (Box 48:, Folder 314)
    - Contract committee minutes, 1939-1942 (Box 48:, Folder 315-320)
    - Jacquard Weaving—change in payment method, 1941 (Box 48:, Folder 321)
    - Data given to union, 1944 (Box 48:, Folder 322)
    - Union agreement—rough draft, 1947 (Box 48:, Folder 323)
    - Union contract to outside firms, 1949-1952 (Box 48:, Folder 324-327)
    - Request for increase in wages, 1941 (Box 48:, Folder 328)
    - Companies agreements list, 1947-1950 (Box 48:, Folder 329)
    - Contracts from outside firms, 1933-1954 (Box 48:, Folder 330-335)
    - Clippings—textile strike, 1934 (Box 48:, Folder 336)
    - Textile strike, 1934 (Box 48:, Folder 337)
    - Winant report—textile strike, 1934 (Box 49:, Folder 338)
    - Clippings—silk strike, 1937 (Box 49:, Folder 339)
    - Velvet weavers, 1941 (Box 49:, Folder 340)
    - Mass layoffs and velvet strike, 1938-1939 (Box 49:, Folder 341)
    - Clippings—strike, 1941 (Box 49:, Folder 342)
    - James Ellis—Administrator of Local #63, 1954-1956 (Box 49:, Folder 343)
    - Union Christmas party, 1946-1950 (Box 49:, Folder 344)
    - Union correspondence, data, dues assignment, 1952 (Box 49:, Folder 345)
    - Wage information given to union, 1952 (Box 49:, Folder 346)
    - Maximum rates list, 1939-1942 (Box 49:, Folder 347)
    - Wage information given to union, 1948 (Box 49:, Folder 348)
    - Labor organization—constitution and bylaws, 1930-1949 (Box 49:, Folder 349)
    - Textiles Workers Union of America—publications, 1948-1949 (Box 49:, Folder 350)
    - Voluntary dues assignment cards, 1948 (Box 49:, Folder 351)
    - TWUA negotiations—contract expiration, 1951 (Box 49:, Folder 352)
    - National wage policy, 1947 (Box 49:, Folder 353)
    - Information given to union, 1956 (Box 49:, Folder 354)
    - Union security, 1948 (Box 49:, Folder 355)
    - Data—union shop elections, 1948 (Box 49:, Folder 356)
    - States forbidding close shop agreements, 1947 (Box 49:, Folder 357)
    - Data—union contract, close shop, 1939-1943 (Box 49:, Folder 358-361)
    - Union committees, 1934 (Box 49:, Folder 362-376)
    - Clippings, 1941, 1946 (Box 49:, Folder 377-378)
    - Manchester Union clippings—union, 1934-1935 (Box 49:, Folder 379)
    - Cheney Brothers' system report, 1935 (Box 49:, Folder 380-381)
    - Grievances submitted by the union, 1934 (Box 49:, Folder 382)
    - United Textile Workers of America, 1934-1935 (Box 49:, Folder 383-384)
    - Local 2125—meeting minutes, 1934-1936 (Box 49:, Folder 385)
    - Voluntary Labor Arbitration rules, 1945-1952 (Box 49:, Folder 386)
    - Arbitration consultant—Rufus S. Paret, 1953 (Box 49:, Folder 387)
    - American Arbitration Association booklets, 1943-1948 (Box 49:, Folder 388)
    - U.S. Department of Labor Arbitration Provisions Correspondence, 1944 (Box 49:, Folder 389)
      - American Arbitration Association, 1939-1951 (Box 49:, Folder 390-392)
      - Local 63, 1938-1959 (Box 49:, Folder 393-401)
        - Inter-office memoranda, 1937-1943 (Box 49:, Folder 402-408)
        - Outside memoranda, 1940-1941 (Box 49:, Folder 409-410)
      - Textile workers Union of America (TWUA)
        - Jacquard weaving, meeting minutes, 1937-1948 (Box 49:, Folder 411-418)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, 1938-1946 (Box 49:, Folder 419-424)
    - Auxiliary division dispute, 1940 (Box 49:, Folder 425)
      - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 49:, Folder 426)
      - Meeting minutes, 1940 (Box 49:, Folder 427)
      - Statements of Cheney Brothers, 1940 (Box 49:, Folder 428)
      - Statements of union, 1940 (Box 49:, Folder 429)
      - Data, 1940 (Box 49:, Folder 430)
    - Velvet Mawaco, 1948 (Box 49:, Folder 431)
  - Subseries C: Arbitration Cases and Awards, 1930-1953
    - TWUA/Apponaug Co./Greenville Finishing Co. (Box 49:, Folder 432)
      - Kenyon Piece Dye Works/Bradford Dyeing
      - Association, 1948
    - TWUA—Fall River-New Bedford Cotton Mfg., 1949 (Box 49:, Folder 433)
    - TWUA—44 New England Cotton Toy Mills (Box 49:, Folder 434)
      - Hayward Schuster Woolen Mills, 1953
    - Hess-Goldsmith Company, 1953 (Box 49:, Folder 435)
    - TWUA v. Tynan Throwing Company/Peterson (Box 49:, Folder 436)
      - Silk Throwing Co./Morris Gorden, Inc., 1953
    - Strike—1923, discussion and monetary standards, 1930 (Box 49:, Folder 437)
  - Subseries D: Disputes, 1920-1951
    - Throwing department-Winding dispute, 1937 (Box 49:, Folder 438)
    - Velvet wet finishing dispute, 1938
      - Meeting minutes (Box 49:, Folder 439)
      - Wages (Box 49:, Folder 440)
      - Tenter
        - Union statements (Box 49:, Folder 441)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 49:, Folder 442)
        - Summary of time studies (Box 49:, Folder 443)
      - U.S. Department of Labor studies conciliation, 1939 (Box 49:, Folder 444)
      - Cheney Brothers' statement, 1938 (Box 49:, Folder 445-446)
      - Reply to union statement, 1938 (Box 49:, Folder 447-448)
      - Arbitration award, 1938 (Box 49:, Folder 449-450)
      - Arbitration award, CT Board of Mediation and Arbitration, 1938 (Box 49:, Folder 451)
    - Velvet Weaving Dispute
      - Meeting minutes, 1938 (Box 49:, Folder 452)
      - Correspondence—American Arbitration Assoc., 1938 (Box 49:, Folder 453)
      - Clippings, 1938-1939 (Box 49:, Folder 454)
      - Synopsis of events after April meeting, 1939 (Box 49:, Folder 455)
      - Statement of dispute, 1939 (Box 49:, Folder 456-457)
      - Award and opinion—American Arbitration Assoc., 1939 (Box 49:, Folder 458)
      - Charts, 1938-1939 (Box 49:, Folder 459)
      - Data, charts, tables, 1939 (Box 49:, Folder 460)
      - Date—piece work, 1939 (Box 49:, Folder 461)
      - Exhibits, 1939 (Box 49:, Folder 462)
      - Synopsis of meetings and exhibits, 1938-1939 (Box 49:, Folder 463)
      - Loomfixers, 1939 (Box 49:, Folder 464)
      - Negotiations, 1940 (Box 49:, Folder 465)
      - Data—wages and hours, 1939-1940 (Box 49:, Folder 466)
    - Wet weaving dispute (Box 50)
      - Data, 1939-1940 (Box 50:, Folder 467)
      - Arbitrators' data, 1939 (Box 50:, Folder 468-470)
      - Competitive costs and C.B. costs, 1939 (Box 50:, Folder 471)
      - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 50:, Folder 472)
      - Agreements—proposed and final, 1939 (Box 50:, Folder 473)
      - Synopsis of meetings, 1938-1939 (Box 50:, Folder 474)
      - Correspondence—TWUA, 1939 (Box 50:, Folder 475)
      - Data and earnings, 1920-1956 (Box 50:, Folder 476)
    - Vacation dispute, 1941 (Box 50:, Folder 477-478)
    - Arbitration award—piece dye house dispute, 1951 (Box 50:, Folder 479)
    - Robinson, Robinson and Cale, 1951 (Box 50:, Folder 480)
    - F7A—piece dye discharge case (Box 50:, Folder 481-482)
    - Discharge cases
      - Dancrosse, Macri, Rowe, Moreau, 1951 (Box 50:, Folder 483)
      - Snipes, William, 1951 (Box 50:, Folder 484)
      - Dugal, Norman, 1951 (Box 50:, Folder 485)
    - NLRB meeting minutes, 1947 (Box 50:, Folder 486)
    - Minutes—past meetings, 1949-1956 (Box 50:, Folder 487)
    - Auxiliary division arbitration
      - Union rates, 1940-1941 (Box 50:, Folder 488)
      - Personnel, 1941 (Box 50:, Folder 489)
      - Work sheets, 1941 (Box 50:, Folder 490)
      - Statistical, 1941 (Box 50:, Folder 491)
    - Auxiliary division arbitration
      - Sources, 1941 (Box 50:, Folder 492)
      - Rates and earnings, 1941 (Box 50:, Folder 493)
    - Minutes
      - Engraving, 1934-1954 (Box 50:, Folder 494)
      - Finishing, 1937-1955 (Box 50:, Folder 495)
      - General, 1939-1955 (Box 50:, Folder 496)
      - Preparation, 1937-1955 (Box 50:, Folder 497)
      - Folding, 1940-1955 (Box 50:, Folder 498)
      - Printing, 1940-1955 (Box 51:, Folder 499)
      - Steam department, 1943-1955 (Box 51:, Folder 500)
      - Yarn division, 1942-1955 (Box 51:, Folder 501)
      - Broad goods, 1950-1955 (Box 51:, Folder 502)
      - Loomfixers and smashpiecers, 1940-1954 (Box 51:, Folder 503)
      - Quilling, spooling and winding, 1937-1955 (Box 51:, Folder 504)
      - Slashing and sizing, 1937-1955 (Box 51:, Folder 505)
      - Trimming, 1939-1955 (Box 51:, Folder 506)
      - Twisting, 1937-1955 (Box 51:, Folder 507)
      - Warping, 1942-1963 (Box 51:, Folder 508)
      - Weaving, 1939-1955 (Box 51:, Folder 509-510)
      - Dressing division, 1937-1941 (Box 51:, Folder 511)
      - Robe department, 1944-1948 (Box 51:, Folder 512)
      - Flare department, 1942-1945 (Box 51:, Folder 513)
      - Cravat shipping, 1943-1947 (Box 51:, Folder 514)
      - Cravat, 1938-1949 (Box 51:, Folder 515)
      - Condition and testing laboratory, 1943-1952 (Box 51:, Folder 516)
  - Subseries E: Local 63, 1934-1955
    - Changes in agreement, 1952 (Box 51:, Folder 517)
    - Dues increase from $0.50 to $0.70, 1952-1955 (Box 51:, Folder 518)
    - Changes in contract, 1947 (Box 51:, Folder 519)
    - Changes in agreement, 1947 (Box 51:, Folder 520)
    - Changes in 1942 agreement, 1942-1947 (Box 51:, Folder 521)
    - Dues increase from $0.35 to $0.50, 1946 (Box 51:, Folder 522)
    - Dues increase from $0.25 to $0.35, 1946 (Box 51:, Folder 523)
    - Correspondence—acknowledgment of union, 1934 (Box 51:, Folder 524)
    - Singed copy of agreement, 1937-1952 (Box 51:, Folder 525-531)
  - Subseries F: Supreme Court of Errors, 1951-1954
    - Wage case reargument, 1954 (Box 51:, Folder 532)
    - Court briefs, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 533)
    - Wage increase, 1951-1954 (Box 51:, Folder 534)
    - Meeting minutes, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 535)
    - Company and Union briefs, 1954 (Box 51:, Folder 536)
    - CT Supreme Court briefs, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 537)
    - Wage case—memorandum of Decisions, 1954 (Box 51:, Folder 538)
    - Memorandum of Decisions, 1954 (Box 51:, Folder 539)
  - Subseries G: Arbitration Local 63, 1938-1974
    - Awards
      - Velvet wet finishing, 1938 (Box 51:, Folder 540)
      - Velvet weaving dispute, 1939 (Box 51:, Folder 541)
      - Auxiliary division dispute, 1941 (Box 51:, Folder 542)
      - Velvet twisting dispute, 1948 (Box 51:, Folder 543)
      - Piece dye house dispute, 1951 (Box 51:, Folder 544)
      - Auxiliary division wage arbitration case, 1954 (Box 51:, Folder 545)
      - William Vennart vacation pay, 1954 (Box 51:, Folder 546)
    - General wage decrease court case—Award and opinion
      - Submission to arbitration, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 547)
      - Memorandum of Decision—Judge Alcorn, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 548)
      - Supoena, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 549)
      - Cheney Brothers brief, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 550)
      - Correspondence—Robinson, Robinson and Cole, 1953-1954 (Box 51:, Folder 551)
      - F. Vaas letter, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 552)
      - Arbitrator's decision and award, 1952 (Box 51:, Folder 553)
      - Press release, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 554)
      - Basic rate of pay, 1938-1940 (Box 51:, Folder 555)
      - Wage increases, 1951-1953 (Box 51:, Folder 556)
      - Notices, 1951-1953 (Box 51:, Folder 557)
      - Cheney Bulletin #37, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 558)
      - Changes in agreement, 1942-1947 (Box 51:, Folder 559)
      - Minutes of union meetings, 1945-1953 (Box 51:, Folder 560)
      - Transcript of evidence corrections, 1953 (Box 51:, Folder 561)
    - Wage decrease case—Fall River and New Bedford
      - Wage reduction of 1952 (Box 51:, Folder 562)
      - Statement of union, 1952 (Box 51:, Folder 563)
      - Statement of employees, 1952 (Box 51:, Folder 564)
    - Superior Court Case, 1952-1954 (Box 51:, Folder 565)
    - Wage reduction case, 1952-1953 (Box 51:, Folder 566)
    - Supreme Court decision, 1954 (Box 52:, Folder 567)
    - Ropes, Gray, Best, Coolidge and Rugg, 1952-1953 (Box 52:, Folder 568)
    - Robinson, Robinson and Cole, 1952-1953 (Box 52:, Folder 569)
    - General Wage arbitration case
      - Correspondence and information—Vaas, 1952 (Box 52:, Folder 570)
      - Cheney Brothers wage data to competitors for exchange, 1952 (Box 52:, Folder 571)
      - Worksheets and competitive wages, 1952 (Box 52:, Folder 572)
      - Correspondence—H.R. Mallery, A. Rhodes, 1952 (Box 52:, Folder 573)
      - Bates case, Duplan brief, 1952 (Box 52:, Folder 574)
      - Arbitration award, 1952 (Box 52:, Folder 575)
      - Correspondence and notices, 1952-1953 (Box 52:, Folder 576)
      - Statement of company, 1952 (Box 52:, Folder 577)
      - Arbitration hearing transcript, 1952 (Box 52:, Folder 578-579)
      - Cheney Brothers exhibits, 1952 (Box 53:, Folder 580)
      - Minutes of union meetings, 1945-1952 (Box 53:, Folder 581)
    - Auxiliary division wage arbitration case
      - TWUA Local 63, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 582)
      - Statement of company and exhibits, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 583)
      - Wage information, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 584)
      - Sources of information and computation, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 585)
      - General information, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 586)
      - Correspondence—American Arbitration Assoc., 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 587)
      - Arbitrator's opinion and award, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 588)
      - Correspondence—Frank Vaas, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 589)
      - Past hearing statement, 1954 (Box 53:, Folder 590)
      - Union statement, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 591)
      - Union's past hearing statement, 1953-1954 (Box 53:, Folder 592)
      - Furnishing tools, duties of employees, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 593)
      - Correspondence—union, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 594)
      - Information to union, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 595)
    - General wage arbitration case, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 596)
      - Union—statements and exhibits, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 597)
      - General meeting, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 598)
      - Correspondence and notice, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 599)
      - Correspondence—American Arbitration Assoc., 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 600)
      - Returned minutes, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 601)
      - Correspondence—Robinson, Robinson and Cole, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 602)
      - Union wage studies, rebuttal material, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 603)
      - Company and union post hearing briefs, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 604)
      - Work sheets and information to union, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 605)
      - Conversion from incentive to day pay, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 606)
      - Correspondence—F. J. Vaas, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 607)
      - Mr. Mallory, Mr. Harry, 1952-1953 (Box 53:, Folder 608)
      - Wage payment policies, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 609)
      - Correspondence, 1946-1953 (Box 53:, Folder 610)
      - Result—general wage increase, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 611)
      - Union correspondence, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 612)
      - Mills moving south, 1946-1953 (Box 53:, Folder 613)
      - Work sheets breakdown—number of employees, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 614)
      - Award and opinion (copies), 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 615)
    - Wage studies work sheets, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 616)
      - Synthetics, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 617)
      - Throwing, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 618)
      - Spun Yarns, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 619)
      - Plushes, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 620)
      - Transparent, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 621)
      - Jacquards, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 622)
      - Maintenance and clerical, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 623)
    - General wage arbitration case, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 624)
      - Earnings comparison, 1951-1953 (Box 53:, Folder 625)
      - Wage study converters, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 626)
      - Effect of wage differential, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 627)
      - August earnings by job class, 1952 (Box 53:, Folder 628)
      - Cheney Brothers earnings by division, 1963 (Box 53:, Folder 629)
    - Wage study distribution of employees, 1963 (Box 53:, Folder 630)
    - Exhibits not to be used in new case, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 631)
    - Related materials, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 632)
    - Background material, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 633)
    - Company supplementary exhibits, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 634)
    - Company statement, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 635)
    - Competitive data, reports, 1953 (Box 53:, Folder 636)
    - Arbitration case—Local 63 vs. Cheney Brothers, 1953 (Box 54:, Folder 637)
      - Transcript of evidence, Superior Court (Box 54:, Folder 638)
        - Case no. L-10717
        - v. I—Company's case (Box 54:, Folder 639)
        - v. II—Union's case (Box 54:, Folder 640)
        - v. III—Company and union rebuttal (Box 54:, Folder 641)
      - Supplementary exhibits
        - A: Wage structure, cotton and synthetic Textiles (Box 54:, Folder 642)
        - B: Report on New England textile industry (Box 54:, Folder 643)
        - C: Meeting minutes, 1945-1953 (Box 54:, Folder 644-645)
        - E: MA report on unemployment compensation, 1950 (Box 54:, Folder 646)
        - Cheney Brothers exhibits, 1953 (Box 55:, Folder 647-648)
    - Letter from W.K. Cole—denial of union's petition of certiorari in wage case, 1955 (Box 55:, Folder 649)
    - Information to union, 1955 (Box 55:, Folder 650)
    - Demand for arbitration—wage increase request, 1956 (Box 55:, Folder 651)
    - Union agreements correspondence, 1962-1974 (Box 55:, Folder 652-654)
    - Union contract, Local 63 TWUA, 1938-1971 (Box 55:, Folder 655-657)
  - Subseries H: Laws, undated, 1947-1954
    - United States Department of Labor
      - Productivity and factory performance, 1953 (Box 55:, Folder 658)
      - Average weekly earnings by industry, 1953-1954 (Box 55:, Folder 659)
      - Employee Assoc. and collective bargaining, 1947, 1952 (Box 55:, Folder 660)
      - Woolens, 1948-1952 (Box 55:, Folder 661)
      - Cotton and rayon, silk and rayon, 1946-1952 (Box 55:, Folder 662)
      - Premium pay, 1943-1945 (Box 55:, Folder 663)
      - Government contract posters, 1945-1951 (Box 55:, Folder 664)
      - Wage and hour division, 1942-1945 (Box 55:, Folder 665)
      - Minimum wage, 1950-1953 (Box 55:, Folder 666)
    - National Labor Relations Act, 1949 (Box 55:, Folder 667)
    - Wagner Act, 1935-1946 (Box 55:, Folder 668)
    - Taft-Hartley Act
      - Taft-Hartleyism in textiles, 1953 (Box 55:, Folder 669)
      - Interpretation of Taft-Hartley Act, 1947-1948 (Box 55:, Folder 670)
      - Operating under Taft-Hartley, 1947 (Box 55:, Folder 671)
      - Article and speeches, 1949-1954 (Box 55:, Folder 672)
    - Digest of Labor-Management Relations Act, 1947 (Box 55:, Folder 673-674)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act (1938), 1938-1949 (Box 55:, Folder 675)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act (1949), 1949-1950 (Box 55:, Folder 676)
    - Walsh-Healey Act
      - Government contracts, 1936-1950 (Box 55:, Folder 677)
      - Aviation textile products manufacturing, undated (Box 55:, Folder 678)
      - Industry, 1942-1951 (Box 55:, Folder 679)
    - Wage regulations under Public Contracts Act, 1945-1954 (Box 55:, Folder 680)
    - Investigations, 1939 (Box 55:, Folder 681)
    - Neckwear industry, 1940 (Box 55:, Folder 682)
    - Textile industry minimum, 1952-1953 (Box 55:, Folder 683)
    - Textile industry, 1936-1944 (Box 55:, Folder 684)
    - Wearing apparel industry, 1938 (Box 55:, Folder 685)
    - Portal to portal Act (Box not specified)
      - Act of 1947 (Box 56:, Folder 686)
      - Effect of Act on fair labor standards, 1938 1947 (Box 56:, Folder 687)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Box 56:, Folder 688)
    - Internal Revenue Act, 1948 (Box 56:, Folder 689)
    - Withholding tax on disability pay, 1955 (Box 56:, Folder 690)
    - Fair Employment Practices Act, 1947 (Box 56:, Folder 691)
    - Sales and Use Tax, 1947-1948 (Box 56:, Folder 692)
- Series IV: Product samples, undated, 1925-1955
  - Silk samples, ca. 1940-1955 (Box 57)
  - Silk samples, undated (Box 130-135)
  - Photographs – an employee outing in 1918 and a silk exhibit at 181 Madison Avenue, New York City, at the Cheney Brothers showrooms in 1925, 1918-1925 (Box 58)
  - Educational charts—silk cultivation and manufacture; samples [see also Box 11—Edgar Brandt], undated (Box 59)
- Series V: General Accounts, 1847-1927
  - Subseries A: Journals, 1847-1876
    - Journal, 1847 June - 1853 July (Box 60)
    - A, 1854 July - 1859 August (Box 61)
    - B, 1859 August - 1860 November (Box 62)
    - C, 1861 July - 1864 January (Box 63)
    - D, 1864 January - 1866 October (Box 64)
    - E, 1866 November - 1868 December (Box 65)
    - F, 1869 June - 1871 April (Box 66)
    - G, 1871 April - 1873 March (Box 67)
    - H, 1873 April - 1874 July (Box 68)
    - I, 1874 August - 1875 November (Box 69)
    - J, 1875 December - 1877 May (Box 70)
    - K, 1877 June - 1878 November (Box 71)
    - L, 1878 December - 1880 May (Box 72)
    - M, 1880 June - 1881 December (Box 73)
    - N, 1882 February - 1883 May (Box 74)
    - O, 1883 June - 1884 August (Box 75)
    - P, South Manchester, 1884 September - 1885 November (Box 76)
    - Q, South Manchester, 1885 November - 1877 January (Box 77)
    - R, South Manchester, 1877 January - 1888 March (Box 78)
    - S, South Manchester, 1888 April - 1889 May (Box 79)
    - T, South Manchester, 1889 June - 1891 February (Box 80)
    - U, South Manchester, 1891 March- 1892 December (Box 81)
    - V, 1893 January - 1895 March (Box 82)
    - W, 1895 April - 1895 March (Box 83)
    - X, 1897 February - 1898 November (Box 84)
    - General accounts and sales journal, 1874 January - 1876 December (Box 85)